http://www.billious.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is critically important to us. At Billiou’s we have a few fundamental principles:
We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
In our communication products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.
Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:
If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our webmaster.
Billiou’s operates a website located at Billious.com. It is Billiou’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Billiou’s collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and
time of each visitor request. Billiou’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Billiou’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Billiou’s may release non-personally-identifying
information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Billiou’s also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our dealer forum. Billiou’s only discloses logged in user and commenter
IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that forum user IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the forum where the
comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Billiou’s website choose to interact with Billiou’s in ways that require Billiou’s to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Billiou’s gathers depends on the nature of the
interaction. For example, we ask dealers who sign up for access to provide complete persoanl information for the verification of accout status with Billiou’s in order to prevent unauthorized sharing of confidential information. In each
case, Billiou’s collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Billiou’s. Billiou’s does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as
described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
Billiou’s may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. For instance, Billiou’s may monitor the most popular articles or links on the Billious.com site and may display this information publicly or provide it to
others. However, Billiou’s does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Billiou’s discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on
Billiou’s behalf or to provide services available at Billiou’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. By using Billiou’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Billiou’s will not rent
or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Billiou’s discloses potentially
personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Billiou’s believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the
property or rights of Billiou’s, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of Billiou’s website and have supplied your email address, Billiou’s may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features,
solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Billiou’s and our products. We primarily use our various product articles to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a
minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users.
Billiou’s takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Billiou’s uses cookies to help Billiou’s identify and track
visitors, their usage of Billiou’s website, and their website access preferences. Billiou’s visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Billiou’s websites,
with the drawback that certain features of Billiou’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Business Transfers
If Billiou’s, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Billiou’s goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third
party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of Billiou’s may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
Ads
Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information
about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by
Automattic and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Billiou’s may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at Billiou’s sole discretion. Billiou’s encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy
Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
